## **SUMMARY**

I have approximately four years of experience being around Agile methodologies and DevOps practices. I like to learn new things and keep current with newly changing technology.

I am seeking to leverage solid technical skills and abilities to advance my career as Software Developer. Finally, I can say that i love how software can impact and solve people's life.

# CONTACT

- +55 61 99281 7070
- EDU-EDUARDO99@HOTMAIL.COM
- VALPARAÍSO DE GOIÁS, GOIÁS, BRAZIL

#### LANGUAGUES

ENGLISH - B2

#### **CORE COMPETENCIES**

- Python
- Java
- Docker
- Kubernetes

# CARLOS EDUARDO SOUSA

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor's of Computer Science University Center of Brasília, Brazil (Jan/2017 - Jul/2021)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Senior Full Stack Developer - 08/2021 to currently Stefanini Group, Brasilia

Allocated at a Brazilian federal accountability office known as TCU.

Applied technologies: Kotlin, Java, Spring, Angular 13, Solr, OracleDB, Kafka, Jenkins, Kubernetes.

Middle Python Developer - 06/2021 to 08/2021 Basis Tecnologia, Brasilia

Allocated at a federal agency linked to the Ministry of Education known as INEP.

Applied technologies: Python3.8, Redis, Oracle DB, Jenkins.

Junior Software Developer - 05/2020 to 05/2021 Basis Tecnologia, Brasilia

Worked as a software developer in the architecture squad; helped in the implementation of SSO - CAS (Spring Webflow/Spring Boot), integrating with Gitlab, Jenkins, SonarQube, internal systems, and Jira Server. Deployed and configured the application in test and production environments, using Kubernetes and Helm. Applied technologies: PDI Client (Spoon), Flask, SQLAlchemy, Angular 11, PostgreSQL, Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes, Helm Charts.

Intern Software Developer - 03/2018 to 04/2020 Basis Tecnologia, Brasilia

Worked as Jira Server Admin, creating workflows, users, screens, issues status, post

functions/validators/listeners (using Groovy).

Designed, coded, and deployed software to automate users' creation process on Jira, which integrates into RocketChat and Admin SDK Google.

Applied technologies: Spring Boot, Spring Cloud Stream, Spring Data, Spring LDAP, Thymeleaf, Spring Mail, Docker, RabbitMQ, Flask (Python), Redis, Jenkins, Kubernetes, Helm Charts.